Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, papers
1991-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Etchemendy, John
Hennessy, John L.
SC0700
177 Linear Feet (130 boxes)
Records from his term as President of Stanford University, along with the records of the Provost. Some of the records were generated by the previous administration of Gerhard Casper.
Information about Access
President's records are restricted 20 years from end of tenure. Materials are otherwise open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Description of the Collection
Records from his term as President of Stanford University, along with the records of the Provost. Some of the records were generated by the previous administration of Gerhard Casper.
Stanford University -- Public Relations.; Stanford University -- Presidents.; Stanford University -- Buildings.; Stanford University -- Administration.; Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Etchemendy, John; Hennessy, John L.; Hennessy, John L.; Etchemendy, John
- President's records, 2000-2001; Accession ARCH-2004-026
  Conditions Governing Access note
  The materials are restricted 20 years from end of tenure.
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 09/30/1999-04/02/2001; AA 1.12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Students/Studies, Issues, 11/30/2000-08/2001; AA 1.13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Emeriti, 09/2000-08/2001; AA 2.2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Development (Faculty Affairs, Misc.), 09/29/2000-08/17/2001; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fellows of the University (Folder A), 09/01/2000-08/31/2001; AA 2.9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fellows of the University (Folder C), 09/01/94-08/31/95; AA 2.9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fellows of the University (Folder B), 09/01/95-08/31/96; AA 2.9 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Teaching & Research Assist/Assoc., 09/25/2000-01/19/2001; AA 2.11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Studies/Issues, 10/10/2000-05/31/2001; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Accreditation Issues / Very General, 05/01/2001-06/26/2001; AA 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - US News/World Rpt. Rankings/Ratings, 02/21/2001; AA 3.5 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ideals/Values (West Culture requirement), 01/01/2000; AA 3.5.1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Studies, 12/15/2000-08/27/2001; AA 3.6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Summer Programs, et al, 07/11/2001; AA 3.16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Summer Programs, et al (folder B), 03/07/2001-08/30/2001; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - School of Humanities & Science(folder A), 09/01/2000-02/23/2001; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 10/20/2000-08/30/2001; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Applied Physics, Dept of, 10/02/2000; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Art, Dept of, 10/01/2000-06/20/2001; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chemistry, Dept of, 11/23/1999-08/29/2001; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dance, Dept of, 01/08/2000-06/18/2001; AA 4.1.16 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Computer Science, Dept of, 08/30/1999-08/15/2001; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Drama, Dept of, 09/09/1999-08/31/2001; AA 4.1.18 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Economics, Dept of, 09/27/1999-06/24/2001; AA 4.1.20 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Inst. for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), 08/31/1999-08/31/2001; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - English, Dept of, 06/21/2000-05/24/2001; AA 4.1.21 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - French & Italian, Dept of, 09/07/1999-06/18/2001; AA 4.1.22 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - German, Dept of, 11/19/1999-01/26/2001; AA 4.1.24 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - History, Dept of, 09/11/2000-08/16/2001; AA 4.1.25 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (HMS), 10/1999-07/20/2000; AA 4.1.28 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Music, Dept of, 10/05/1999-08/2001; AA 4.1.29 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Music, Dept of (folder B), 01/02/2001-08/06/2001; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Athletics, Dept of (folder A), 02/26/1999-12/05/2000; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Football Games, Tyrone Willingham - Rose Bowl, etc., 09/14/2000-08/04/2001; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 11/12/1999-08/10/2001; AA 4.1.32 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Physics, Dept of, 01/01/2000-07/03/2001; AA 4.1.33 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Political Science Department, 09/21/1999-08/30/2001; AA 4.1.34 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Psychology, Dept of, 12/13/1999-07/09/2001; AA 4.1.35 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Graduate School of Business, 09/01/2000-08/30/2001; AA 4.2 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 09/03/1999-07/19/2001; AA 4.3 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Engineering, School of, 08/09/2000-08/27/2001; AA 4.4 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Education, School of, 09/22/2000-08/15/2001; AA 4.5 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Hoover Institute (folder A), 11/27/2000-12/31/2000; AA 4.9 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Hoover Institute (folder B), 01/04/2001-08/29/2001; AA 4.9 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Hoover Institute (folder C)Hoover Library, 11/2000-12/2000; AA 4.9 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Libraries at Stanford (general catch-all), 10/03/2000-08/24/2001; AA 4.12 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Law School (Folder A), 10/25/2000-02/27/2001; AA 4.15 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Law School (Folder B), 03/19/2001-08/28/2001; AA 4.15 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Awards/Prizes, Misc., 09/18/2000-08/15/2001; AA 5 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Grants, Scholarships, Misc., 09/11/2000-08/31/2001; AA 6 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Information, 12/01/2000-08/15/2001; AA 8 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Tanner Fellowship, 1998-07/31/2001; AA 9.19 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, 09/13/1999-08/30/2001; AA 10 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Stanford, Miscelleneous, Stanfordiana, 10/20/1999-08/16/2001; AD 1 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Historical Society, Stanford, 10/10/1999-03/01/2001; AD 1.2 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Honor Code/Fundamental Standard, 08/07/2000-08/01/2001; AD 3.10 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - President's Office, 05/98-06/17/2001; AD 4 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - President's Workshop on Gender Equality, 01/09/2001; AD 4.3 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Sweden Stuff related to Learning Lab, 10/04/1999-08/02/2001; AA 4.10.4 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - University Cabinet, 09/01/1999-07/05/2001; AD 4.13 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - General Correspondences, 09/12/2000-12/14/91; AD 4.20 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Condolence Letters, 09/01/1999-08/16/2001; AD 4.20.2 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 09/19/2000-05/15/2001; AD 4.20.3 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 10/03/2000-08/28/2001; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Invitations(Folder A), 09/01/2000-05/01/2001; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Invitations (Folder B), 04/12/2001-08/31/2001; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Casper's Resignation Folder A, 09/08/1999-09/14/99; AD 4.20.4/3 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Casper's Resignation Folder B, 09/15/1999-09/27/99; AD 4.20.4/3 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Casper's Resignation Folder C, 10/01/1999-09/2000; AD 4.20.4/3 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Nonsense Folder A, 09/07/2000-03/29/2001; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Nonsense Folder B, 04/09/2001-05/21/2001; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - NonsenseFolder C, 06/04/2001-08/31/2001; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters (search letters), 09/08/2000-08/17/2001; AD 4.20.6 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Complaint Letters, 10/16/00 - 08/28/2001; AD 4.20.7 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder A, 09/12/00 - 02/26/2001; AD 4.20.8 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder B, 3/01/01 - 03/30/2001; AD 4.20.8 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder C, 04/02/01 - 05/29/2001; AD 4.20.8 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder D, 06/01/2001-08/31/2001; AD 4.20.8 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - University Communications, 10/16/00 - 05/22/2001; AD 4.22 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Office of Campus Relations, 09/20/00 - 08/23/2001; AD 6 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Admissions (Folder A), 09/26/2000-08/14/2001; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Admissions (Folder B), 09/18/1999-08/29/2000; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of, 9/8/99 - 8/23/2000; AD 8.8 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Overseas Studies Programs, 04/07/98 - 8/9/2001; AD 8.11 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 08/16/00 - 07/25/2001; AD 8.18 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, 09/17/98-08/06/2001; AD 8.18.11 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 09/28/2001-05/23/2001; AD 8.21 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, 10/09/2000-08/30/2001; AD 10 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Employment Inquiries/Requests (Folder A), 09/12/2000-03/01/2001; AD 10.1 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Employment Inquiries/Requests (Folder B), 01/03/2000-08/10/2000; AD 10.1 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Media - All Forms - External, 11/14/2000-08/15/2001; AD 11.8 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Stanford University Press, 11/14/2000-07/31/2001; AD 11.8.9 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Surveys, Studies, Questionnaires, 08/10/2001; AD 11.8.10 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Media, Internal, 10/02/2000-08/09/2001; AD 11.8.11 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Business and Finance, 09/13/2000-07/16/2001; AD 12.2 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Administrative Resources, 35640; AD 12.2/3 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Stanford Management Company, 10/18/2000-11/27/2000; AD 12.3 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Tuition, 10/13/1999-02/01/2001; AD 12.5.4 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Vice President for Development, 09/26/2000-05/03/2001; AD 12.10 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Office of Development, 04/19/2000-05/03/2001; AD 12.10.1 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - President's Fund, 09/01/1999-03/29/2001; AD 12.10.2/2 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - The Stanford Fund (FOLDER A), 10/17/2000-05/07/2001; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - The Stanford Fund (FOLDER B), 09/01/1999-08/31/2000; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Development, Events, 09/01/1999-07/28/2000; AD 12.10.2/5 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Donor Relations, 11/23/1999-04/17/2001; AD 12.10.2/7 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Asian Relations, General, 09/22/2000-007/19/2001; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all Folder A, 06/15/2001-08/27/2001; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all Folder B, 03/26/2001-06/13/2001; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all Folder C, 3/10/00 - 5/19/2000; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all Folder D, 10/25/2000-04/02/2001; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Wattis Room, 09/24/1998-06/04/2001; AD 12.14 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Housing, Land and Building Issues Community Plan GUP Folder A, 07/27/2001-07/07/2000; AD 12.14.1 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Housing, Land and Building Issues Community Plan GUP Folder B, 08/03/2000-11/99; AD 12.14.1 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Housing, Land and Building Issues Community Plan GUP Folder C, 09/02/1999-08/02/2000; AD 12.14.1 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Facilities / Planning / Univ. Architect, 09/15/2000-08/15/2001; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Memorial Church, 09/08/1999-05/01/2001; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Parking/Transportation, 09/27/1999-07/31/2001; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Conferences, Misc., 10/17/2000-07/26/2001; AD 13.10.1 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Industrial Relations, 09/19/2000-05/22/2001; AD 15 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Alumni Relations, 11/29/2000-07/18/2001; AL 1 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Parent's Club (formerly known as "Mother's Club"), 09/23/1999-04/03/2001; AL 1.1/1 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student) Folder A, 08/01/2001-08/31/2001; AL 1.3 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student) Folder B, 05/14/2001-07/30/2001; AL 1.3 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student) Folder C, 09/11/2000-04/28/2001; AL 1.3 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Annual Graduate Mailing, 09/01/1999-08/14/2000; AL 1.4 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Alumni Conference/Homecoming, 10/16/1999-07/06/2001; AL 1.7 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Alumni Association, 06/01/2000-01/04/2001; AL 3 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - SAA - 2000 (Stanford Alumni Association), 09/12/2000-08/20/2001; AL 3.1 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Alumni Giving (OOD), 09/15/1999-07/25/2001; AL 5 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Board of Trustees, 09/01/2000-08/24/2001; B 1 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 12/11/2000-02/22/2001; C 2 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Academic Council - Advisory Board, 09/06/2000-05/02/2001; C 3 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - University Committees, 12/17/1999-08/29/2001; C 6 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - General Gov't Info., 12/01/2000-07/23/2001; G 1 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - California State Government, 09/15/2000-08/22/2001; G 1.2 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Department of Defense (DoD), 07/09/2001-08/10/2001; G 3.7 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Department of Energy (DoE), 12/14/1999-08/01/2001; G 3.7.2 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Department of Education, U.S. (USDE), 09/17/1999-08/03/2001; G 3.8.3 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 10/16/2000-08/21/2001; G 3.19 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Local Government / Local Business, 04/23/2001-08/06/2001; G 4 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Foreign Government Relations, misc., 11/27/2000-06/27/2001; G 5 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Hospital Administration, 11/18/98 - 6/29/2000; SHS 3 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Patient Relations [empty], SHS 14 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Misc. Medical School Departments Folder B), 09/12/2000-08/07/2001; M 5 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations (Folder A), 09/05/2000-01/30/2001; O 1 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations (Folder B), 02/02/2001-06/16/2001; O 1 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations (Folder C), 06/01/2001-08/24/2001; O 1 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, 09/14/1999-05/25/2001; G 7 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 09/20/1999-10/17/2000; G 10 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Children's Hospital, 10/26/98-08/09/2001; SHS 7 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 9/25/2000-08/31/2001; M 1 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Medical School Development, 11/29/1999-07/16/2001; M 2 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Misc. Medical School Departments Folder A), 09/03/1999-08/31/2000; M 5 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Misc. Medical School Misc, 11/28/2000-03/20/2001; M 5 - Crangle (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Education Groups, 09/29/2000-08/29/2001; O 3 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 12/13/2000-07/18/2001; O 3.1 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Association Pacific Rim University, 09/04/1999-08/20/2001; O 3.4 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - American Adademy of Arts and Sciences, 10/26/2000-08/20/2001; O 3.7 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - American Council on Education, 9/22/99 - 8/22/2000; O 3.8 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - National Assocation of Independent Colleges & Univ., 09/30/1999-07/06/2001; O 3.10 (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 09/25/2000-08/09/2001; O 3.43 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) (Folder A), 05/11/2001-06/22/2001; O 3.44 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) (Folder A), 08/17/2000-10/26/2000; O 3.44 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 09/01/2000-08/06/2001; O 3.47 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - CA Business Higher Education Forum, 10/24/2000-01/16/02; O 3.56 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - University Research Association, 06/01/2000-06/20/2001; O 7.16 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Other Colleges and Universities (Folder A), 09/01/2000-03/15/2001; O 8 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Other Colleges and Universities (Folder B), 03/26/2001-08/31/2001; O 8 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - American Association of Universities, 5/17/00 - 8/18/2000; O 8.7 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - American Association of Universities, 1/4/00 - 5/15/2000; O 8.7 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Students (Misc.), 9/21/99 - 7/25/2000; ST 1 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Student (Groups), 10/31/99 - 3/31/2000; ST 1.1 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Bechtel International Center, 10/10/2000-08/17/2001; ST 3.5 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Student/Parent Correspondence, 9/13/99 - 8/3/2000; ST 8 (Box 9, Folder 174)
- President's records, 2002-2003; Accession ARCH-2005-173
  - Provost's Office, 09/01/1999-08/19/2003; AA 1 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 09/21/2001-11/12/2001; AA 1.12 (Box 1)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 11/21/1999-06/20/2001; AA 1.2 (Box 1)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, 09/10/2002-08/21/2003; AA 10 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Studies/Issues, 09/19/2002-08/29/2003; AA 3 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation Issues / Very General, 10/29/2001-06/23/2003; AA 3.4 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Sciences, 11/11/2001-08/23/2003; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - Dance, Dept of, 03/20/2002-10/30/02; AA 4.1.16 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Inst. for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), 02/10/2003-07/28/2003; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1)
  - Athletics, Dept of, 10/17/2001-07/22/2003; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1)
  - Libraries at Stanford (general catch-all), 12/02/2002-08/29/2003; AA 4.12 (Box 1)
  - Law School (Folder A), 09/2002; AA 4.15 (Box 1)
  - Law School (Folder A), 10/2002-08/2003; AA 4.15 (Box 1)
  - Information Technology Service (ITS), 02/27/2002-07/31/2003; AA 4.22 (Box 1)
  - Engineering, School of, 11/19/2002-07/15/2003; AA 4.4 (Box 1)
  - Education, School of, 04/04/2002-08/28/2003; AA 4.5 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institute(folder A), 09/05/2002-08/28/2003; AA 4.9 (Box 1)
  - Awards/Prizes, Misc., 09/23/2002-08/27/2003; AA 5 (Box 1)
  - Grants, Scholarships, Misc., 10/24/2001-07/29/2003; AA 6 (Box 1)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Information, 10/09/2002-08/25/2003; AA 8 (Box 1)
  - Fullbright Fellowship/Scholarship, 02/04/2000-10/07/02; AA 8.16 (Box 1)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, 11/16/1999-08/15/2003; AA 8.17 (Box 1)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 09/01/1999-06/23/2003; AA 8.25 (Box 1)
  - Terman Fellowship, 09/30/1999-12/20/02; AA 8.30 (Box 1)
  - Tanner Lectures, 01/18/2002-03/10/2003; AA 9.19 (Box 1)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, 09/10/2002-08/21/2003; AA 10 (Box 1)
  - General Correspondences, 09/18/2002-08/25/2003; AD 4.20 (Box 2)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 10/08/2002-08/14/2003; AD 4.20.3 (Box 2)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 08/13/2003-08/05/2003; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 2)
  - Invitations(Folder A), 08/31/2003-11/01/02; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2)
  - Invitations( Folder B), 09/01/2002-10/31/2003; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2)
  - Invitations(Folder C), 05/01/2002-08/30/02; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2)
  - Invitations(Folder D), 12/01/2002-04/30/02; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2)
  - Nonsense, 03/01/2003-8/27/2003; AD 4.20.5 (Box 2)
  - Nonsense, 09/01/2002-02/01/2003; AD 4.20.5 (Box 2)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters (search letters), 01/22/2003-05/29/2003; AD 4.20.6 (Box 2)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder A, 01/01/2003-08/31/2003; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder B, 11/01/2003-02/27/2003; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder C, 09/09/2002-10/31/02; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder D, 06/01/2002-08/31/02; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3)
  - Solicitation Letters (General) Folder E, 04/01/2002-05/30/02; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3)
  - Admissions, 08/31/2003-09/24/02; AD 8.1 (Box 3)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 05/23/1999-06/18/2003; AD 8.18 (Box 3)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, 01/17/2002-07/11/2003; AD 8.18.11 (Box 3)
  - Residential Education, 11/29/2000-07/31/2003; AD 8.18.13 (Box 3)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 11/05/2001-08/15/2003; AD 8.21 (Box 3)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of, 12/06/2002-07/31/2003; AD 8.8 (Box 3)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations (FOLDER A), 06/01/2003-08/31/2003; AD 10 (Box 3)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations (FOLDER B), 05/01/2003-05/31/2003; AD 10 (Box 3)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations (FOLDER C), 01/01/2003-04/15/2003; AD 10 (Box 3)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations (FOLDER D), 09/01/2002-10/01/02; AD 10 (Box 3)
  - Lively Arts at Stanford, 09/29/2000-03/29/02; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 3)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 09/03/1999-04/25/2003; AD 11.7.7 (Box 3)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all, 10/31/2002-08/20/2003; AD 12.14 (Box 4)
  - Task Force on Alumni Relations, 12/12/2001-04/10/2003; AL 1.2 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student) Folder A, 08/25/2001-10/29/02; AL 1.3 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student) Folder B, 11/04/2002-01/22/2003; AL 1.3 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student) Folder C, 02/14/2003-07/17/2003; AL 1.3 (Box 4)
  - Annual Graduate Mailing, 08/14/97 & 08/19/02; AL 1.4 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Conference/Homecoming, 09/28/2001-06/06/2003; AL 1.7 (Box 4)
  - SAA - 2000 (Stanford Alumni Association), 11/05/2001-02/11/2003; AL 3.1 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Giving (OOD), 04/11/2002-11/07/2003; AL 5 (Box 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 09/01/2001-08/08/2003; B 1 (Box 4)
  - Board of Trustees Appointments, 11/08/2000-08/27/2003; B 12 (Box 4)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 10/03/2000-07/29/02; B 14 (Box 4)
  - Trustee Committee on Land & Use Building Campus Plng, 11/29/1999-08/18/2003; B 14.6 (Box 4)
  - Academic Council, 11/05/1999-06/16/2003; C 1 (Box 4)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 11/12/2001-06/19/2003; C 2 (Box 4)
  - Academic Council - Steering Committee - STC, 10/05/1999-03/05/2001; C 4.1 (Box 4)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education, 09/01/2002-08/31/2003; C 5.7.1 (Box 4)
  - General Gov't Info., 12/16/2002-07/07/2003; G 1 (Box 4)
  - California State Government, 09/01/2002-08/31/2003; G 1.2 (Box 4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 09/01/2002-08/31/2003; G 2.3 (Box 4)
  - U.S. Governmental Relations, 09/01/2002-08/31/2003; G 3 (Box 4)
  - Department of Defense (DoD), 10/15/2002-07/10/2003; G 3.7 (Box 4)
  - Department of Energy (DoE), 10/28/2002-04/07/2003; G 3.7.2 (Box 4)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA), 12/05/2002-08/08/2003; G 3.7.4 (Box 4)
  - Health & Human Services, Office of Civil Rights, 09/11/2002-08/25/2003; G 3.8.1 (Box 4)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 07/02/2002-11/10/2003; G 3.8.2 (Box 4)
  - Department of Education, U.S. (USDE), 09/01/2002-08/19/2003; G 3.8.3 (Box 4)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 09/16/2002-05/27/2003; G 3.19 (Box 4)
  - Local Government / Local Business, 09/01/2001-06/16/2003; G 4 (Box 4)
  - Foreign Government Relations, misc., 10/16/2002-08/27/2003; G 5 (Box 4)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, 12/02/2002-08/08/2003; G 7 (Box 4)
  - UCSF/SHC-1 MERGER, 09/01/1998-06/01/2001 (Box 5)
  - School of Medicine Administration (Folder A), 10/03/2002-04/28/2003; M 1 (Box 6)
  - School of Medicine Administration (Folder B), 05/13/2003-08/20/2003; M 1 (Box 6)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations (Folder A), 09/02/2002-10/30/02; O 1 (Box 6)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations (Folder B), 11/05/2002-12/30/02; O 1 (Box 6)
  - Misc Ad- Hoc Organization (Folder C), 01/06/2003-03/31/2003; O 1 (Box 6)
  - Misc Ad- Hoc Organization (Folder D), 04/01/2003-05/27/2003; O 1 (Box 6)
  - Misc Ad- Hoc Organization (Folder E), 06/03/2003-08/27/2003; O 1 (Box 6)
  - Council of Competitiveness, 09/25/2002-06/12/2003; O 1.2 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities (AAC&U), 10/07/2002-10/25/02; O 3 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 07/10/2003; O 3 (Box 6)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 01/22/2003-03/24/2003; O 3 (Box 6)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 09/25/2001-07/15/2003; O 3.1 (Box 6)
  - Association Pacific Rim University, 09/27/2001-08/25/2003; O 3.4 (Box 6)
  - American Adademy of Arts and Sciences, 09/04/2002-12/03/02; O 3.7 (Box 6)
  - American Council on Education, 10/02/2002-08/13/2003; O 3.8 (Box 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 09/17/2002-07/1403; O 3.43 (Box 7)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA)Folder A), 08/20/2002-08/26/2003; O 3.44 (Box 7)